So we have this encounter with the crystalline anlage, we enlarge it in evolution,
所以我们有了晶体胚芽的相遇，我们将其放大演变，
and what do we see?
我们看到了什么？
We see that there is a space here, that this epiblast that comes to
我们看到这里有一个空间，这个外胚层附着在这里，
attach, you see, look at the change of shape here, you see,
你看，注意这里形状的变化，你看，
and what is there inside, the black, what can I say that I find as fluid there?
那里面是什么？黑色的部分，我能说那里有什么液体？
CSF, okay, and here what fluid do I have there?
脑脊液，好的，那这里有什么液体？
the amniotic, same origin, you see. And here, we will see
羊水，同源的，你看。这里，我们将看到
that there is a juxtacrine communication,
存在旁分泌通讯，
molecular connection, and also, we see the path
分子连接，而且，我们还看到了
of a vessel, which is the first wave
一条血管的路径，这是第一波
of one of the tunics of the eye, which is called the choroid.
眼球壁之一，我们称之为脉络膜。
The choroid, it will form the vascular tissue
脉络膜将形成眼球的血管组织。
of the eye. And so, it's really an...
所以，这真是一个...
An invasion that comes there.
一个入侵来到了这里。
Four important levels to have an artery, you remember, or a vessel.
要有动脉或血管，有四个重要的层面，你们还记得吗？
Trajectory, you said one, three more.
轨迹，你已经说了一个，还有三个。
Well, there are all the components, presence of vesicles, presence of a chemical gradient,
嗯，有所有的组成部分，囊泡的存在，化学梯度的存在，
presence of these different actions, of these different things to form
这些不同作用、不同事物的存在，以形成
a vessel.
一根血管。
And so we have this coloboma cleft through which these vessels will pass here.
所以我们有这个哥伦布裂隙，血管将在这里穿过。
These are called hyaloid vessels, which will later transform into retinal vessels,
我们称之为玻璃体血管，它们以后会变成视网膜血管，
etc.
等等。
And so we see this communication, you see, between the epiblast,
所以我们看到了这种沟通，你看，在外胚层之间，
and this part here will be called, so initially it was
而这一部分将被称为，所以最初它被称为
called the primary optic vesicle,
原发性视泡，
when it starts to form this kind of small plate, the end of the cup, you see, of the calyx,
当它开始形成这种小盘子，杯状的末端，你看，像圣杯一样，
here, with this connection here.
在这里，与这里的连接。
It's called the secondary optic vesicle.
这叫做次级视泡。
It's the same tissue that is here.
它和这里的组织是相同的。
And this, this will be called what we call the inner layer and the outer layer
而这，将被称为我们所说的视网膜的内层和外层。
of the retina.
视网膜的。
So we see here the retinal space with its
所以我们在这里看到了视网膜空间，以及它的
inner layer and its outer layer.
内层和外层。
So that means that this vision...
所以这意味着这种视觉...
Primary optic vesicle coming
原发性视泡，最终来自
from the brain, ultimately, will become what we call the space
大脑，将成为我们所说的
of the retina.
视网膜空间。
Anatomists, embryologists, consider that the retina, it
解剖学家、胚胎学家认为，视网膜，
is really this external brain that has been put in place.
它确实是这个外在的大脑。
With the importance of this cerebrospinal fluid, these informations that
伴随着脑脊液的重要性，这些信息
will remain on a point.
将停留在一点上。
plane of the intercellular exudate,
细胞间渗出液平面，
and the crystalline vesicle, lens,
以及晶状体囊泡，晶状体，
which will come, it, from the surface epiblast.
它将来自表面外胚层。
So it's an encounter through juxtacrine communication.
因此，这是通过近分泌通讯实现的相遇。
If you take it back here, it's as if it will suddenly,
如果你再看这里，就好像它会突然间，
poof, it will leave and there will remain a surface epithelium
砰，它会离开，留下一个表面上皮
and a lens that will be taken inside,
和一个被包裹在里面的晶状体，
as my neural tube had formed.
就像我的神经管形成一样。
Same scheme, same idea.
同样的图示，同样的想法。
So we see this lens here.
所以我们在这里看到了这个晶状体。
And we see that the skin here, which will be there,
我们看到这里的皮肤，它将在这里，
will be found on the surface with different levels that we will study.
将以我们即将研究的不同层次出现在表面。
Among others, this crystalline tissue which will form, among others,
其中，这个晶状体组织将形成
the very first layer of the eye.
眼睛的第一层。
You look at your neighbor's eye, etc.
你看看你邻居的眼睛，等等。
You actually see one sixth of the eye.
你实际上看到了眼睛的六分之一。
But the first layer, very first layer,
但第一层，最第一层，
layer, first membrane that arrives
层，第一层膜到达
there in front, it's called the conjunctiva
前面，它被称为结膜
which is a tissue
它是一种组织
in fact, which will be found on the
事实上，它将出现在
future eyelids, etc. but which will line
未来的眼睑等，但它将覆盖
the surface of the eye
眼睛的表面
then you have
然后你有
a space in the lens here
这里晶状体中的一个空间
in the crystalline lens
在晶状体中
which will form the chamber
它将形成前房
in front, because it will divide
因为它会分裂
the space in front
前面的空间
of the eye, and which will divide
眼睛的，它将分裂
into two spaces, into chambers
成两个空间，即房
called anterior and posterior, and the lens that will be put in place.
称为前房和后房，以及将就位的晶状体。
And here, we have the retina which is thin, thin, thin, like a cigarette paper.
在这里，我们有视网膜，它非常非常薄，就像一张